Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series IB: General Files, I-Z
  - International Botanical Congress, 1963-1967 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - International Conference on Health and Health Education, 1962 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - International Congress of Genetics, 1963-1968 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - International Congress of Human Genetics (Third), 1966 (Box 184, Folder 11-12)
  - International Congress of Human Genetics, abstracts and summaries of papers presented, 1966 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Mathematicians, 1962-1967 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Onomastic Science, 1966 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Orientalists, 1964-1965 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - International Congress on Tropical Medicine and Malaria, 1962-1963 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1961-1963 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - International Cooperation Administration, Institute of Inter-American Affairs, progress reports, Chilean Project, 1956-1966 (Box 185, Folder 7-8)
  - International Economic History Conference, 1960-1962 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - International Education Act, 1966-1967 (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - International Educational Exchange Programs, exchange visitors program, 1961-1967 (Box 185, Folder 11)
  - International Educational Exchange Programs, exchange visitors program, immigrations laws and rulings, 1963 (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - International Educational Exchange Programs, French exchange fellowships and professorships, 1961-1966 (Box 185, Folder 13)
  - International, general, 1964-1968 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - International Geological Congress, 1964 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - International Honors Program, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - International House, 1960-1968 (Box 186, Folder 4-6)
  - International House, approvals by the Board of Trustees, budget, 1961-1966 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - International House Association, 1961 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - International House, background material, 1931-1965 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - International House, Board of Governors, 1962-1964 (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - International House, Board of Governors, 1965-1968 (Box 187, Folder 1-2)
  - International House, Board of Governors, Committee on Membership and Nominations, 1961-1968 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - International House, Board of Governors, Executive Committee, 1962-1967 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - International House, Board of Governors, minutes, 1961-1968 (Box 187, Folder 5-6)
  - International House, Board of Governors, notices of meetings, agenda and attendance, 1960-1967 (Box 187, Folder 7-8)
  - International House, Board of Governors, notices of meetings, agenda and attendance, 1968 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - International House, budgets, 1967-1968 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - International House, Committee on Organization and Management of, 1930-1961 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - International House, Executive Director, 1962 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - International House, operating and financial statements, 1961-1967 (Box 188, Folder 5-7)
  - International House, relationships to Board of University of Chicago, site negotiations, 1927-1968 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - International Medical Conference on Congenital Malformations, 1961-1962 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - International Monetary Problem, some unsettled issues, conference on, 1966 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - International Peace Conference of University Professors, 1962-1963 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - International Project for the Evaluation of Educational Achievement (IEA), 1967 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - International Student Cooperative Union, 1963 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - International Track, 1962-1964 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - International Union of Biological Sciences, 1961-1962 (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - International Union of Pure and Applied Physics, 1965 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Inter-University Center for Japanese Studies, Tokyo, 1967-1968 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Inter-University Conference on the Negro in Higher Education, 1963 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Inter-University Conference on the Negro in Higher Education, second, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Inter-University Consortium for Political Research, 1962-1965 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Insurance, 1961-1962 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Investment policy press luncheon, 1968 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Investments, 1952-1963 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Investments, 1965-1968 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Investments, changes in stock holdings, 1961-1965 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Iowa, University of, 1964-1966 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Ireland, 1963-1967 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Irish Fellowship Club, 1955-1963 (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Israel, 1961-1968 (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - J-, general, 1963-1967 (Box 190, Folder 1-3)
  - Japan, visitors to the University of Chicago from, 1965-1968 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Japanese Studies, Centers of, report by James Morley, Columbia University, 1967 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Japanese visitor, Prince Takahito Mikasa, 1964-1965 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Japanese visitors to the University of Chicago, 1961-1962 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Jesuit Research Council of America, 1962-1967 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Chautauqua Society, 1954-1967 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Children's Bureau of Chicago, 1961-1964 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Federation of Metropolitan Chicago, 1962-1968 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - John Hopkins University, 1957-1966 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - John Hopkins University Founders' Day Commemoration, February 22, 1965 (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, President Lyndon B., 1963-1968 (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Joint Committee on Study of Education for Public Health, 1961-1962 (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - Joint Council to Improve the Health Care of the Aged, 1962-1963 (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - Joint Directory of Higher Education, 1961 (Box 190, Folder 17)
  - Jon-, general, 1965-1966 (Box 190, Folder 18)
  - Journal of Higher Education, 1962 (Box 190, Folder 19)
  - Junior Achievement, 1961-1962 (Box 190, Folder 20)
  - Junior Achievement of Chicago, 1963 (Box 190, Folder 21)
  - Junior Association of Commerce and Industry, 1961-1965 (Box 190, Folder 22-24)
  - Junior Association of Commerce and Industry, United States, Jaycees, 1967-1968 (Box 190, Folder 25)
  - Juvenile Delinquency Project, 1961-1967 (Box 190, Folder 26)
  - K-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Kappa Delta Pi, Omega chapter, 1961-1962 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Ke-, general, 1963-1966 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy Foundation, 1963 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, President and Mrs. John F., 1961-1968 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., the Honorable, 1964-1968 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Kent State University, 1958-1964 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Kentucky, University of, 1965-1966 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence Alpheus, portrait, 1960-1962 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence Alpheus, University of Illinois honorary degree, 1961 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Kimpton, Marcia Drennon, (Mrs. Lawrence A.), 1955-1963 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Kiwanis International, 1961-1968 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - Kn-, general, 1965 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Kuppenheimer, Albert B., Fund, Advisory Committee on the, 1967-1968 (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - Laboratories for Applied Sciences, 1961 (Box 191, Folder 15)
  - Laboratories for Applied Sciences, 1962-1965 (Box 192, Folder 1-3)
  - Laboratories for Applied Sciences, Faculty Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Laboratories for Applied Sciences, staff, 1961-1965 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory Schools, 1960-1965 (Box 192, Folder 6-8)
  - Laboratory Schools, 1966-1968 (Box 193, Folder 1-3)
  - Laboratory Schools, admission policies, 1963-1967 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Schools, accreditation, evaluation by the Independent Schools Association of the Central States, 1965 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory Schools, Committee on the Scholarship Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory Schools, directorship of precollegiate directorship, 1961-1964 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory Schools, personnel, policies, 1964-1968 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory Schools, principals, 1965-1967 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory Schools, space, 1966-1967 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Lake Forest Academy, 1967 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Lake Forest College, 1960-1968 (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
  - Lakeside Conference XII, 1961 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Lakeside Planning Conference XIII, 1962 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Lakeside Planning Conference XIV, 1963 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Language Laboratory, 1960-1966 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - La Rabida Jackson Park Sanitarium, 1960-1962 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Latin Department, 1953-1965 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Laubach Literacy, 1966 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Law School, 1961-1962 (Box 194, Folder 10-11)
  - Law School, 1963-1967 (Box 195, Folder 1-6)
  - Law School, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Law School, accreditation, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Law School, Comparative Law Research Center, 1964 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Law School, deanship, 1962-1968 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Law School, deanship, comments on appointment of Phil C. Neal, 1963 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Law School, Jury Project, 1962-1967 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Law School, Law Review, 1962-1967 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Law School, lectures, 1959-1964 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Law School, space, 1964-1965 (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Law School Visiting Committee, 1960-1968 (Box 196, Folder 10-12)
  - League of Women Voters, 1955-1968 (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - Learning Resources Institute, 1961 (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - Lectures, general, 1958-1968 (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
  - Lectures, offers, 1961-1968 (Box 197, Folder 3-4)
  - Lectureships, Barnes, Kathryn, Memorial Lectures, 1967 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Lectureships, Carlson, Anton J., Memorial Lectures, 1964-1966 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Lectureships, Encyclopaedia Britannica Lecture Series, 1963-1967 (Box 197, Folder 7-9)
  - Lectureships, Encyclopaedia Britannica Lecture Series, Committee on, 1963-1967 (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Lectureships, Freund, Ernst, 1962-1966 (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - Lectureships, Harper, Paul V., 1962-1963 (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - Lectureships, Haskell and Barrows Lectures, Committee on, membership, 1961-1964 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Lectureships, Moody, William Vaughn, 1961-1968 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Lectureships, Ruml, Beardsley, Colloquia of the division of the Social Sciences, 1966-1967 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Lectureships, Schaffner, Sarah H., 1966-1967 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Lectureships, Student Government, Ogden lecture series, V. P. Humphrey, 1966 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Lectureships, Student Government, Wm. B. Ogden Memorial lecture series, 1964-1966 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Lectureships, Towle, Charlotte, Lectures, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Lectureships, Walgreen, Charles Rudolf, Foundation Lectures on American Institutions, 1967 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Lectureships, White, Alexander, Lectureship, 1963-1965 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Legal Office, 1961-1968 (Box 198, Folder 10-12)
  - Lehigh University, 1964 (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Leukemia research, 1961-1964 (Box 198, Folder 14)
  - Levi, Edward H., article, Law Schools and the Universities, 1965 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Levi, Edward H., budget talk, 1967-1968 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Levi, Edward H., correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 199, Folder 3-4)
  - Levi, Edward H., correspondence, Provost, 1962-1966 (Box 199, Folder 5-7)
  - Levi, Edward H., regrets, 1964 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Levi, Edward H., speeches, 1968 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Levi, Edward H., speeches, convocation speech, June 11 and 12, 1965 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Levi, Edward H., speeches, National Leadership Conference, 1966 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Levi, Edward H., speeches to freshmen (orientation), 1967 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Levi, Edward H., speeches, the University and the Community, University of Chicago Club of Washington, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Levi, Edward H., speeches, the University and the Modern Condition, University of Chicago Citizen's Board, 1967 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Levi, Edward H., talk, Liberal Arts Conference, 1966 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Libraries, 1961-1968 (Box 200, Folder 7-10)
  - Libraries, annual reports, 1960-1963 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Libraries at other institutions, comparative statistics, 1961-1965 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Libraries, space, 1961-1965 (Box 201, Folder 3-4)
  - Library Associates, proposed, 1962 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Library, Board of the, 1961-1967 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Library, Board of the, membership, 1961-1968 (Box 201, Folder 7-8)
  - Library, Board of the, membership, list of members, 1945-1963 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Library of International Relations, 1961 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Library Planning and Building, Committee on the (advisory), 1963-1965 (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Library Resources and Development, Committee on, 1961-1962 (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Library School, Graduate, 1961-1962 (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Library School, Graduate, 1961-1968 (Box 202, Folder 1-3)
  - Library School, Graduate, deanship, 1961-1968 (Box 202, Folder 4-5)
  - Library School, Graduate, facilities and space, 1964-1965 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Library, University, Department of Special Collections, exhibitions, "Hebraica" exhibit, 1965 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Library, University, Department of Special Collections, Monroe, Harriet, Modern Poetry Collection, 1949-1965 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Library, University, Director's annual reports, 1966-1967 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Library, University, Directorship, 1953-1968 (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Library, University, Harper, William Memorial Library, Pace Associations Study, 1963 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - Library, University needs, 1961-1966 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Library, University, photo duplication services, 1962-1967 (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Library, University, policies, practices and procedures, 1963-1968 (Box 202, Folder 14)
  - Library, University, Regenstein, Joseph, building, lights and lighting controls, 1966 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Library, University, Regenstein, Joseph, Library, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 2-3)
  - Library, University, Regenstein, Joseph, Library, Committee to review the plan of, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Library, University, Science Library, Committee on the, 1961-1966 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Library, University, staff and personnel, professional appointments, 1961-1967 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Life magazine, 1961-1968 (Box 203, Folder 7-8)
  - Life Sciences Center, proposed Bioscience Development Center, 1965-1966 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Lighting, campus, 1965-1966 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Lighting of campus and buildings, Commonwealth Edison exterior lighting recommendations, 1966 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln Academy of Illinois, 1964-1967 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1959-1964 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Linear, Inc., Dr. Ernest H. Wakefield, 1963 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Linguistics, Atlas proposal, Linguistic Institute, 1952-1962 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Linguistics, Department of, 19601-1966 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1940-1966 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Liquor control ordinance, local option campaigns and elections, Woodlawn area, 1966 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Listening Post, 1961-1968 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Loan funds, employee emergency, 1963-1967 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Loan programs, student loan programs, guaranteed loans, 1966 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Loan programs, students, 1960-1968 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Long Island University, 1967-1968 (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Look magazine, 1958-1966 (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Loomis School, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Times, 1966-1968 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Lovanium University, Belgian Congo, 1961 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Loyola University, 1961-1968 (Box 205, Folder 3-5)
  - Lutheran School of Theology, site negotiations, 1962-1967 (Box 205, Folder 6-9)
  - Lutherans, 1963-1967 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Lutherans, possible move to University of Chicago campus, 1961 (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Lybrand, Ross Brothers and Montgomery, 1961-1968 (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - Lying-In Hospital, 1961-1968 (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - Lying-In Hospital, Board of Directors, 1961-1966 (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - Lying-In Hospital, courtesy staff, 1962-1967 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Lying-In Hospital, Mother's Aid Dinner, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - M-, general, 1963-1968 (Box 206, Folder 3-4)
  - Macalester College, 1961-1967 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - MacMurray College, 1959-1968 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Madison, James, papers, 1961-1968 (Box 206, Folder 7-8)
  - Mandel Hall, activities, 1962-1967 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Mandel loan fund, applications, 1958-1963 (Box 206, Folder 10-13)
  - Mandel loan fund, applications, 1964-1967 (Box 207, Folder 1-4)
  - Mandeville, Paul, 1952-1961 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Mangold, KP, 1961 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Maroon, 1961-1964 (Box 207, Folder 7-8)
  - Marquette University, 1961-1962 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Marshals and aides, 1961-1968 (Box 207, Folder 10-11)
  - Marshals and aides, student marshals and aides, 1961-1968 (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Marts and Lundy, 1959-1962 (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - Mason, Max, 1925-1967 (Box 207, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1960-1962 (Box 207, Folder 15-17)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1964-1968 (Box 208, Folder 1-2)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, salary information exchange, 1961-1966 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, University of Chicago meetings, 1963-1965 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts, University of, 1966-1967 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Mass communications media, proposed commission, 1961-1963 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Mass media of communication, 1953-1965 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 208, Folder 8-11)
  - Mathematics, Department of, applied mathematics, 1961-1962 (Box 208, Folder 12)
  - May, Ben, Laboratory, 1961-1963 (Box 208, Folder 13)
  - May, Ben, Laboratory for Cancer Research, 1964-1968 (Box 208, Folder 14)
  - Mayo Clinic Mayo Foundation, 1959-1965 (Box 208, Folder 15)
  - McAfee, Wallace T., 1959-1961 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - McCarran Act, National Committee to Repeal the, 1965 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - McDowell, Mary Settlement, 1961-1964 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - McLaughlin, Andrew C., 1953-1963 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Meadville Theological School, 1961-1968 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Meadville Theological Seminary, affiliation agreements, 1962-1967 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Medical and Biological Research, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Medical and Biological Research Council, 1950s-1967 (Box 209, Folder 8-12)
  - Medical and Biological Research Council, associate program, 1966-1967 (Box 209, Folder 13)
  - Medical and Biological Research Council, membership, 1961-1964 (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, 1961-1965 (Box 209, Folder 15)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, art cart program, 1963-1964 (Box 209, Folder 16)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, Chaplaincy service ant Office of Religion and Health, 1961-1966 (Box 209, Folder 17)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, comments on service, 1961-1968 (Box 209, Folder 18)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, Committee on, 1960-1963 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, Department of Nursing, 1960-1967 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, inhalation therapy education fund, school, 1963-1966 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center, Hospitals and Clinics, Superintendent, 1961-1967 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Medical Clinics, Inside Information, 1958-1963 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Medical education bills, 1960-1967 (Box 210, Folder 6-7)
  - Medical Education for National Defense, 1960-1962 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Medical International Cooperation Organization, 1961-1963 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Medical News, 1966 (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Medical School and Clinics, 1961-1962 (Box 210, Folder 11-12)
  - Medical School and Clinics, 1963 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Medical School and Clinics, the University of Chicago Hospitals and Clinics, 1964 (Box 211, Folder 2-6)
  - Medical School Clinics, Auxiliary Committee of Membership, 1961-1968 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Medical School Clinics, Zoller Memorial Dental Clinic, 1961-1968 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Medical School Clinics, Zoller Memorial Dental Clinic, 25th commemorative year, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, space, 1962 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Medicare, Medicaid, 1962-1967 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Medicine, Department of, 1961-1962 (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - Medicine, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 212, Folder 1-8)
  - Medicine, Department of, chairmanship, 1961-1968 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Medicine, Department of, testimonial dinner for Walter L. Palmer and Joseph B. Kirsner, 1961-1962 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Medicine, Department of, University of Chicago Trivandrum Medical College High Radiation Study, proposed, 1962 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Medicine, Pritzker School of, outside comments on renaming school, 1968 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, Committee on, faculty student, 1967 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, Faculty-Student Committee on, 1966-1968 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Scholarship Fund, proposed, policy on, 1966 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Memorial services, 1961-1967 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Memorials and Portraits, Committee on, 1961-1967 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Mental Retardation Facilities Act, 1963-1967 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Merrill-Palmer Institute, 1961-1968 (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - Meteorology, Department of, 1961-1967 (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - Methodist Church, 1961-1965 (Box 213, Folder 12)
  - Methodist program at the University of Chicago, 1965 (Box 213, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council, 1961-1967 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council, Jack Meltzer study of programs to rebuild Chicago, 1966 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Miami, University of, 1968 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Miami, University of, Florida, 1963-1965 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Michael Reese Hospital, 1961-1968 (Box 214, Folder 5-6)
  - Michael Reese Hospital discussions, Trustees Ad Hoc Committee on, 1968 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Michelson Laboratory, Michelson, Albert A., 1948-1967 (Box 214, Folder 8-9)
  - Michigan State University, 1962-1968 (Box 214, Folder 10-11)
  - Michigan State University, Center for the Study of Higher Education, "Utilization of Instructional Facilities at University of Chicago," 1961 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Michigan State University, Disaster Control Plan, 1965 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Michigan, University of, 1956-1968 (Box 215, Folder 3-6)
  - Michigan, University of, Butter, Dr. Irene, 1964-1965 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Michigan, University of, 1965 research project on costs and returns of graduate education, 1966-1967 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Michigan, University of, report on discrimination, 1966 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Microbiology, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, 1961-1962 (Box 216, Folder 1-2)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, agency agreements, audits and certificates, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, cash and commitment statements, 1962-1967 (Box 216, Folder 4-6)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, property acquisition reports, 1960-1965 (Box 216, Folder 7-8)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, property improvement suspense account reports, 1960-1967 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, property transfer reports, 1960-1965 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Midway Travel Service, John Stock Travel Service, 1949-1962 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Midwest Administration Center, 1962-1967 (Box 216, Folder 12)